
const words2 = [
    { question: "koira", answer: "dog", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
    { question: "kissa", answer: "cat", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
    { question: "auto", answer: "car", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
    { question: "talo", answer: "house", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
    { question: "puu", answer: "tree", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
    { question: "kukka", answer: "flower", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
  /*  { question: "kala", answer: "fish", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
    { question: "lintu", answer: "bird", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
    { question: "hevonen", answer: "horse", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
    { question: "lehmä", answer: "cow", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
    { question: "sika", answer: "pig", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
    { question: "kana", answer: "chicken", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
    { question: "lammas", answer: "sheep", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
    { question: "vuohi", answer: "goat", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
    { question: "susi", answer: "wolf", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
    { question: "karhu", answer: "bear", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
    { question: "hirvi", answer: "moose", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
    { question: "jänis", answer: "rabbit", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
    { question: "orava", answer: "squirrel", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
    { question: "kettu", answer: "fox", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
    { question: "jääkarhu", answer: "polar bear", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
    { question: "pingviini", answer: "penguin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
    { question: "krokotiili", answer: "crocodile", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
    { question: "käärme", answer: "snake", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
    { question: "leijona", answer: "lion", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },*/
    { question: "tiikeri", answer: "tiger", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
    { question: "norsu", answer: "elephant", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
    { question: "apina", answer: "monkey", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
    { question: "gorilla", answer: "gorilla", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
    { question: "kirahvi", answer: "giraffe", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
    { question: "virtahepo", answer: "hippopotamus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 }
];

//kaikki sanoja.js sanat taulukkoon
const words = [
      { question: "ability", answer: "kyky", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "able", answer: "pystyä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "abortion", answer: "abortti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "about", answer: "noin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "above", answer: "edellä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "abroad", answer: "ulkomailla", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "absence", answer: "poissaolo", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "absolute", answer: "absoluuttinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "absolutely", answer: "ehdottomasti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "absorb", answer: "omaksua", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "abuse", answer: "väärinkäyttö", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "academic", answer: "akateeminen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "accept", answer: "hyväksyä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "access", answer: "pääsy", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "accident", answer: "onnettomuus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "accompany", answer: "seurata", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "accomplish", answer: "suorittaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "according", answer: "mukaan", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "account", answer: "tili", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "accurate", answer: "tarkka", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "accuse", answer: "moittia", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "achieve", answer: "saavuttaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "achievement", answer: "saavutus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "acid", answer: "happo", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "acknowledge", answer: "tunnustaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "acquire", answer: "hankkia", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "across", answer: "poikki", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "act", answer: "toimia", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "action", answer: "toiminta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "active", answer: "aktiivinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "activist", answer: "aktivisti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "activity", answer: "toiminta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "actor", answer: "näyttelijä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "actress", answer: "näyttelijä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "actual", answer: "todellinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "actually", answer: "itse asiassa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "ad", answer: "ilmoitus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "adapt", answer: "sopeuttaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "add", answer: "lisätä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "addition", answer: "lisäys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "additional", answer: "lisä-", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "address", answer: "osoite", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "adequate", answer: "riittävä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "adjust", answer: "säätää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "adjustment", answer: "säätö", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "administration", answer: "antaminen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "administrator", answer: "järjestelmänvalvoja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "admire", answer: "ihailla", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "admission", answer: "pääsy", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "admit", answer: "myöntää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "adolescent", answer: "nuori", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "adopt", answer: "hyväksyä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "adult", answer: "aikuinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "advance", answer: "ennakko", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "advanced", answer: "pitkälle kehittynyt", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "advantage", answer: "etu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "adventure", answer: "seikkailu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "advertising", answer: "mainonta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "advice", answer: "neuvot", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "advise", answer: "neuvoo", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "adviser", answer: "neuvonantaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "advocate", answer: "edustaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "affair", answer: "asia", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "affect", answer: "vaikuttaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "afford", answer: "olla varaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "afraid", answer: "peloissaan", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "african", answer: "afrikkalainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "african-american", answer: "afrikkalais-amerikkalainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "after", answer: "jälkeen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "afternoon", answer: "iltapäivällä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "again", answer: "uudelleen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "against", answer: "vastaan", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "age", answer: "ikä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "agency", answer: "virasto", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "agenda", answer: "esityslista", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "agent", answer: "agentti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "aggressive", answer: "aggressiivinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "ago", answer: "sitten", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "agree", answer: "olla samaa mieltä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "agreement", answer: "sopimus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "agricultural", answer: "maatalous", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "ah", answer: "ah", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "ahead", answer: "eteenpäin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "aid", answer: "apu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "aide", answer: "avustaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "aids", answer: "aids", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "aim", answer: "tavoite", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "air", answer: "ilma", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "aircraft", answer: "ilma-alus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "airline", answer: "lentoyhtiö", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "airport", answer: "lentokenttä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "album", answer: "albumi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "alcohol", answer: "alkoholi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "alive", answer: "elossa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "all", answer: "kaikki", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "alliance", answer: "liittouma", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "allow", answer: "sallia", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "ally", answer: "liittolainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "almost", answer: "melkein", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "alone", answer: "yksin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "along", answer: "pitkin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "already", answer: "jo", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "also", answer: "myös", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "alter", answer: "muuttaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "alternative", answer: "vaihtoehto", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "although", answer: "siitä huolimatta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "always", answer: "aina", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "am", answer: "olen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "amazing", answer: "hämmästyttävä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "american", answer: "amerikkalainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "among", answer: "keskuudessa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "amount", answer: "määrä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "analysis", answer: "analyysi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "analyst", answer: "analyytikko", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "analyze", answer: "analysoida", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "ancient", answer: "muinainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "and", answer: "ja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "anger", answer: "suututtaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "angle", answer: "kulma", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "angry", answer: "vihainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "animal", answer: "eläin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "anniversary", answer: "vuosipäivä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "announce", answer: "ilmoittaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "annual", answer: "vuotuinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "another", answer: "toinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "answer", answer: "vastaus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "anticipate", answer: "ennakoida", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "anxiety", answer: "levottomuus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "any", answer: "minkä tahansa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "anybody", answer: "kukaan", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "anymore", answer: "enää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "anyone", answer: "kukaan", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "anything", answer: "mitä tahansa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "anyway", answer: "joka tapauksessa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "anywhere", answer: "missä tahansa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "apart", answer: "erilleen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "apartment", answer: "huoneisto", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "apparent", answer: "näennäinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "apparently", answer: "ilmeisesti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "appeal", answer: "vetoomus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "appear", answer: "ilmestyä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "appearance", answer: "ulkomuoto", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "apple", answer: "omena", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "application", answer: "hakemus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "apply", answer: "käytä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "appoint", answer: "nimittää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "appointment", answer: "nimittäminen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "appreciate", answer: "arvostaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "approach", answer: "lähestyä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "appropriate", answer: "sopiva", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "approval", answer: "hyväksyminen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "approve", answer: "hyväksyä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "approximately", answer: "suunnilleen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "arab", answer: "arabi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "architect", answer: "arkkitehti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "area", answer: "alue", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "argue", answer: "väitellä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "argument", answer: "perustelu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "arise", answer: "nousta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "arm", answer: "käsivarsi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "armed", answer: "aseellinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "army", answer: "armeija", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "around", answer: "noin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "arrange", answer: "järjestää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "arrangement", answer: "järjestely", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "arrest", answer: "pidätys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "arrival", answer: "saapuminen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "arrive", answer: "saapua", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "art", answer: "taide", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "article", answer: "artikla", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "artist", answer: "taiteilija", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "artistic", answer: "taiteellinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "as", answer: "kuten", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "asian", answer: "aasialainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "aside", answer: "syrjään", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "ask", answer: "kysyä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "asleep", answer: "unessa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "aspect", answer: "näkökohta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "assault", answer: "hyökkäys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "assert", answer: "assert", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "assess", answer: "arvioida", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "assessment", answer: "arviointi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "asset", answer: "etu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "assign", answer: "assign", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "assignment", answer: "toimeksianto", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "assist", answer: "avustaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "assistance", answer: "apu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "assistant", answer: "avustaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "associate", answer: "kumppani", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "association", answer: "yhdistys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "assume", answer: "olettaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "assumption", answer: "olettamus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "assure", answer: "vakuuttaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "at", answer: "at", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "athlete", answer: "urheilija", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "athletic", answer: "urheilu-", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "atmosphere", answer: "ilmapiiri", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "attach", answer: "liittää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "attack", answer: "hyökkäys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "attempt", answer: "yrittää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "attend", answer: "osallistu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "attention", answer: "huomio", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "attitude", answer: "asenne", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "attorney", answer: "asianajaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "attract", answer: "vetää puoleensa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "attractive", answer: "viehättävä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "attribute", answer: "ominaisuus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "audience", answer: "yleisö", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "author", answer: "kirjailija", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "authority", answer: "auktoriteetti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "auto", answer: "auto", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "available", answer: "saatavilla", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "average", answer: "keskiverto", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "avoid", answer: "välttää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "award", answer: "palkinto", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "aware", answer: "tietoinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "awareness", answer: "tietoisuus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "away", answer: "pois", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "awful", answer: "hirveä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "baby", answer: "vauva", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "back", answer: "takaisin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "background", answer: "tausta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "bad", answer: "huono", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "badly", answer: "huonosti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "bag", answer: "laukku", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "bake", answer: "leipoa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "balance", answer: "saldo", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "ball", answer: "pallo", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "ban", answer: "kieltää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "band", answer: "bändi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "bank", answer: "pankki", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "bar", answer: "baari", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "barely", answer: "tuskin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "barrel", answer: "tynnyri", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "barrier", answer: "este", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "base", answer: "pohja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "baseball", answer: "baseball", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "basic", answer: "perustiedot", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "basically", answer: "pohjimmiltaan", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "basis", answer: "perusta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "basket", answer: "kori", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "basketball", answer: "koripallo", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "bathroom", answer: "kylpyhuone", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "battery", answer: "akku", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "battle", answer: "taistelu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "be", answer: "olla", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "beach", answer: "ranta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "bean", answer: "papu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "bear", answer: "karhu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "beat", answer: "lyödä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "beautiful", answer: "kaunis", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "beauty", answer: "kauneus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "because", answer: "koska", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "become", answer: "tulla", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "bed", answer: "sänky", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "bedroom", answer: "makuuhuone", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "beer", answer: "olut", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "before", answer: "ennen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "begin", answer: "alkaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "beginning", answer: "alku", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "behavior", answer: "käytös", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "behind", answer: "takana", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "being", answer: "olento", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "belief", answer: "uskomus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "believe", answer: "uskoa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "bell", answer: "soittokello", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "belong", answer: "kuulua", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "below", answer: "alla", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "belt", answer: "vyö", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "bench", answer: "penkki", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "bend", answer: "mutka", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "beneath", answer: "alla", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "benefit", answer: "hyöty", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "beside", answer: "vieressä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "besides", answer: "sitä paitsi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "best", answer: "parhaat", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "bet", answer: "veto", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "better", answer: "paremmin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "between", answer: "välillä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "beyond", answer: "ulkopuolella", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "bible", answer: "raamattu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "big", answer: "iso", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "bike", answer: "pyörä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "bill", answer: "laskuttaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "billion", answer: "miljardi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "bind", answer: "sitoa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "biological", answer: "biologinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "bird", answer: "lintu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "birth", answer: "syntymä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "birthday", answer: "syntymäpäivä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "bit", answer: "bitti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "bite", answer: "purra", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "black", answer: "musta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "blade", answer: "terä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "blame", answer: "syyttää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "blanket", answer: "viltti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "blind", answer: "sokea", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "block", answer: "lohko", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "blood", answer: "veri", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "blow", answer: "isku", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "blue", answer: "sininen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "board", answer: "lauta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "boat", answer: "vene", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "body", answer: "ruumis", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "bomb", answer: "pommi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "bombing", answer: "pommitus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "bond", answer: "side", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "bone", answer: "luu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "book", answer: "kirja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "boom", answer: "puomi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "boot", answer: "saapas", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "border", answer: "reunus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "born", answer: "syntynyt", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "borrow", answer: "lainata", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "boss", answer: "pomo", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "both", answer: "molemmat", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "bother", answer: "vaivautua", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "bottle", answer: "pullo", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "bottom", answer: "pohja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "boundary", answer: "raja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "bowl", answer: "kulho", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "box", answer: "laatikko", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "boy", answer: "poika", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "boyfriend", answer: "poikaystävä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "brain", answer: "aivot", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "branch", answer: "haara", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "brand", answer: "brändi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "bread", answer: "leipä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "break", answer: "tauko", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "breakfast", answer: "aamiainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "breast", answer: "rinta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "breath", answer: "hengitys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "breathe", answer: "hengittää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "brick", answer: "tiili", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "bridge", answer: "silta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "brief", answer: "lyhyt", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "briefly", answer: "lyhyesti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "bright", answer: "kirkas", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "brilliant", answer: "loistava", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "bring", answer: "tuoda", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "british", answer: "brittiläinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "broad", answer: "laaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "broken", answer: "rikki", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "brother", answer: "veli", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "brown", answer: "ruskea", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "brush", answer: "harjata", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "buck", answer: "pukki", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "budget", answer: "talousarvio", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "build", answer: "rakentaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "building", answer: "rakennus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "bullet", answer: "luoti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "bunch", answer: "kimppu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "burden", answer: "taakka", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "burn", answer: "polttaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "bury", answer: "haudata", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "bus", answer: "bussi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "business", answer: "liiketoiminta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "busy", answer: "kiireinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "but", answer: "mutta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "butter", answer: "voi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "button", answer: "nappi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "buy", answer: "ostaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "buyer", answer: "ostaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "by", answer: "mennessä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "cabin", answer: "hytti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "cabinet", answer: "kaappi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "cable", answer: "kaapeli", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "cake", answer: "kakku", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "calculate", answer: "laskea", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "call", answer: "puhelu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "camera", answer: "kamera", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "camp", answer: "leiri", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "campaign", answer: "kampanja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "campus", answer: "kampus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "can", answer: "voida", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "canadian", answer: "kanadalainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "cancer", answer: "syöpä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "candidate", answer: "ehdokas", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "cap", answer: "korkki", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "capability", answer: "valmiudet", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "capable", answer: "kykenevä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "capacity", answer: "kapasiteetti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "capital", answer: "iso alkukirjain", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "captain", answer: "kapteeni", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "capture", answer: "kaapata", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "car", answer: "auto", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "carbon", answer: "hiili", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "card", answer: "kortti-", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "care", answer: "hoito", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "career", answer: "ura", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "careful", answer: "varovainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "carefully", answer: "huolellisesti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "carrier", answer: "kantaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "carry", answer: "carry", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "case", answer: "tapaus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "cash", answer: "käteinen raha", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "cast", answer: "valettu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "cat", answer: "kissa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "catch", answer: "ottaa kiinni", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "category", answer: "kategoria", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "catholic", answer: "katolinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "cause", answer: "syy", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "ceiling", answer: "katto", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "celebrate", answer: "juhlia", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "celebration", answer: "juhla", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "celebrity", answer: "julkkis", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "cell", answer: "solu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "center", answer: "keskusta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "central", answer: "keskus-", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "century", answer: "vuosisata", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "ceo", answer: "toimitusjohtaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "ceremony", answer: "seremonia", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "certain", answer: "tietty", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "certainly", answer: "varmasti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "chain", answer: "ketju", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "chair", answer: "tuoli", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "chairman", answer: "puheenjohtaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "challenge", answer: "haaste", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "chamber", answer: "kammio", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "champion", answer: "mestari", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "championship", answer: "mestaruus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "chance", answer: "mahdollisuus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "change", answer: "muuttaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "changing", answer: "vaihtaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "channel", answer: "kanava", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "chapter", answer: "luku", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "character", answer: "merkki", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "characteristic", answer: "luonteenomainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "characterize", answer: "luonnehtivat", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "charge", answer: "maksu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "charity", answer: "hyväntekeväisyys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "chart", answer: "kartoittaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "chase", answer: "ajojahti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "cheap", answer: "halpa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "check", answer: "tarkistaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "cheek", answer: "poski", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "cheese", answer: "juusto", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "chef", answer: "kokki", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "chemical", answer: "kemiallinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "chest", answer: "rinta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "chicken", answer: "kana", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "chief", answer: "päällikkö", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "child", answer: "lapsi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "childhood", answer: "lapsuus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "chinese", answer: "kiinalainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "chip", answer: "siru", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "chocolate", answer: "suklaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "choice", answer: "valinta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "cholesterol", answer: "kolesteroli", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "choose", answer: "valita", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "christian", answer: "kristillinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "christmas", answer: "joulu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "church", answer: "kirkko", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "cigarette", answer: "savuke", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "circle", answer: "ympyrä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "circumstance", answer: "seikka", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "cite", answer: "siteerata", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "citizen", answer: "kansalainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "city", answer: "kaupunki", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "civil", answer: "siviili-", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "civilian", answer: "siviili-", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "claim", answer: "vaatimus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "class", answer: "luokka", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "classic", answer: "klassikko", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "classroom", answer: "luokkahuone", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "clean", answer: "puhdas", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "clear", answer: "asia selvä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "clearly", answer: "selvästi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "client", answer: "asiakas", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "climate", answer: "ilmasto", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "climb", answer: "kiivetä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "clinic", answer: "klinikka", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "clinical", answer: "kliininen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "clock", answer: "kello", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "close", answer: "kiinni", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "closely", answer: "tarkasti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "closer", answer: "lähemmäksi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "clothes", answer: "vaatteet", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "clothing", answer: "vaatetus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "cloud", answer: "pilvi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "club", answer: "klubi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "clue", answer: "vihje", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "cluster", answer: "rykelmä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "coach", answer: "valmentaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "coal", answer: "kivihiili", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "coalition", answer: "koalitio", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "coast", answer: "rannikko", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "coat", answer: "takki", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "code", answer: "koodi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "coffee", answer: "kahvi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "cognitive", answer: "kognitiivinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "cold", answer: "kylmä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "collapse", answer: "romahtaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "colleague", answer: "kollega", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "collect", answer: "kerätä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "collection", answer: "kokoelma", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "collective", answer: "kollektiivinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "college", answer: "college", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "colonial", answer: "siirtomaa-", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "color", answer: "väri-", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "column", answer: "sarake", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "combination", answer: "yhdistelmä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "combine", answer: "yhdistää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "come", answer: "tulla", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "comedy", answer: "komedia", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "comfort", answer: "mukavuus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "comfortable", answer: "mukava", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "command", answer: "komento", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "commander", answer: "komentaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "comment", answer: "kommentti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "commercial", answer: "kaupallinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "commission", answer: "komissio", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "commit", answer: "tehdä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "commitment", answer: "sitoutuminen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "committee", answer: "komitea", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "common", answer: "yhteinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "communicate", answer: "tiedottaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "communication", answer: "viestintä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "community", answer: "yhteisö", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "company", answer: "yhtiö", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "compare", answer: "vertailla", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "comparison", answer: "vertailu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "compete", answer: "kilpailla", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "competition", answer: "kilpailu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "competitive", answer: "kilpailukykyinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "competitor", answer: "kilpailija", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "complain", answer: "kannella", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "complaint", answer: "valitus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "complete", answer: "saattaa loppuun", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "completely", answer: "täysin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "complex", answer: "monimutkainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "complicated", answer: "monimutkainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "component", answer: "komponentti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "compose", answer: "säveltää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "composition", answer: "sävellys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "comprehensive", answer: "kattava", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "computer", answer: "tietokone", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "concentrate", answer: "keskity", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "concentration", answer: "keskittyminen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "concept", answer: "konsepti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "concern", answer: "koskea", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "concerned", answer: "huolestunut", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "concert", answer: "konsertti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "conclude", answer: "solmia", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "conclusion", answer: "johtopäätös", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "concrete", answer: "betoni", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "condition", answer: "kunto", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "conduct", answer: "käytös", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "conference", answer: "konferenssi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "confidence", answer: "luottamus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "confident", answer: "luottavainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "confirm", answer: "vahvistaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "conflict", answer: "konflikti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "confront", answer: "kohdata", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "confusion", answer: "sekaannus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "congress", answer: "kongressi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "congressional", answer: "kongressin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "connect", answer: "kytkeä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "connection", answer: "yhteys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "consciousness", answer: "tietoisuus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "consensus", answer: "yhteisymmärrys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "consequence", answer: "seuraus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "conservative", answer: "konservatiivinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "consider", answer: "harkita", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "considerable", answer: "huomattava", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "consideration", answer: "harkinta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "consist", answer: "muodostuvat", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "consistent", answer: "johdonmukainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "constant", answer: "jatkuva", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "constantly", answer: "alituisesti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "constitute", answer: "muodostaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "constitutional", answer: "perustuslaillinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "construct", answer: "rakentaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "construction", answer: "rakentaminen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "consultant", answer: "konsultti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "consume", answer: "kuluttaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "consumer", answer: "kuluttaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "consumption", answer: "kulutus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "contact", answer: "ottaa yhteyttä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "contain", answer: "sisältää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "container", answer: "kontti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "contemporary", answer: "nykyajan", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "content", answer: "sisältö", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "contest", answer: "kilpailu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "context", answer: "konteksti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "continue", answer: "jatkaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "continued", answer: "jatkui", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "contract", answer: "sopimus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "contrast", answer: "kontrasti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "contribute", answer: "edistävät", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "contribution", answer: "panos", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "control", answer: "ohjaus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "controversial", answer: "kiistanalainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "controversy", answer: "kiista", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "convention", answer: "sopimus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "conventional", answer: "tavanomainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "conversation", answer: "keskustelu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "convert", answer: "muuntaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "conviction", answer: "vakaumus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "convince", answer: "vakuuttaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "cook", answer: "kokki", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "cookie", answer: "pikkuleipä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "cooking", answer: "ruoanlaitto", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "cool", answer: "viileä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "cooperation", answer: "yhteistyö", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "cop", answer: "poliisi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "cope", answer: "selviytyä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "copy", answer: "kopio", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "core", answer: "ydin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "corn", answer: "maissi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "corner", answer: "kulma", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "corporate", answer: "yritys-", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "corporation", answer: "yhtiö", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "correct", answer: "oikea", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "correspondent", answer: "kirjeenvaihtaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "cost", answer: "kustannus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "cotton", answer: "puuvilla", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "couch", answer: "sohva", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "could", answer: "voisi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "council", answer: "neuvosto", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "counselor", answer: "ohjaaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "count", answer: "kreivi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "counter", answer: "laskuri", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "country", answer: "maa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "county", answer: "lääni", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "couple", answer: "pari", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "courage", answer: "rohkeus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "course", answer: "kurssi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "court", answer: "tuomioistuin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "cousin", answer: "serkku", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "cover", answer: "peite", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "coverage", answer: "kattavuus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "cow", answer: "lehmä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "crack", answer: "crack", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "craft", answer: "alus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "crash", answer: "romahdus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "crazy", answer: "hullu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "cream", answer: "kerma", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "create", answer: "luoda", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "creation", answer: "luominen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "creative", answer: "luova", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "creature", answer: "olento", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "credit", answer: "luotto", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "crew", answer: "miehistö", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "crime", answer: "rikollisuus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "criminal", answer: "rikollinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "crisis", answer: "kriisi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "criteria", answer: "kriteeri", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "critic", answer: "kriitikko", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "critical", answer: "kriittinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "criticism", answer: "kritiikki", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "criticize", answer: "arvostella", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "crop", answer: "sato", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "cross", answer: "ylittää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "crowd", answer: "väkijoukko", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "crucial", answer: "ratkaiseva", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "cry", answer: "itkeä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "cultural", answer: "kulttuurinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "culture", answer: "kulttuuri", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "cup", answer: "kuppi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "curious", answer: "utelias", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "current", answer: "nykyinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "currently", answer: "tällä hetkellä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "curriculum", answer: "opetussuunnitelma", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "custom", answer: "mukautettu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "customer", answer: "asiakas", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "cut", answer: "leikata", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "cycle", answer: "sykli", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "dad", answer: "isä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "daily", answer: "päivittäin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "damage", answer: "vahingoittaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "dance", answer: "tanssi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "danger", answer: "vaara", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "dangerous", answer: "vaarallinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "dare", answer: "uskaltaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "dark", answer: "tumma", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "darkness", answer: "pimeys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "data", answer: "data", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "date", answer: "päivämäärä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "daughter", answer: "tytär", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "day", answer: "päivä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "dead", answer: "kuollut", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "deal", answer: "sopimus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "dealer", answer: "jakaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "dear", answer: "rakas", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "death", answer: "kuolema", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "debate", answer: "keskustelu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "debt", answer: "velka", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "decade", answer: "vuosikymmen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "decide", answer: "päättää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "decision", answer: "päätös", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "deck", answer: "laivan kansi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "declare", answer: "julistaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "decline", answer: "aleneminen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "decrease", answer: "vähennys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "deep", answer: "syvä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "deeply", answer: "syvästi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "deer", answer: "peura", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "defeat", answer: "tappio", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "defend", answer: "puolustaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "defendant", answer: "vastaaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "defense", answer: "puolustus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "defensive", answer: "puolustava", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "deficit", answer: "alijäämä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "define", answer: "määritellä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "definitely", answer: "ehdottomasti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "definition", answer: "määritelmä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "degree", answer: "aste", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "delay", answer: "viive", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "deliver", answer: "toimittaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "delivery", answer: "toimitus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "demand", answer: "kysyntä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "democracy", answer: "demokratia", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "democrat", answer: "demokraatti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "democratic", answer: "demokraattinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "demonstrate", answer: "osoittaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "demonstration", answer: "esittely", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "deny", answer: "kieltää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "department", answer: "osasto", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "depend", answer: "riippua", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "dependent", answer: "riippuvainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "depending", answer: "riippuen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "depict", answer: "kuvaavat", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "depression", answer: "masennus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "depth", answer: "syvyys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "deputy", answer: "sijainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "derive", answer: "johdetuilla", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "describe", answer: "kuvata", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "description", answer: "kuvaus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "desert", answer: "aavikko", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "deserve", answer: "ansaita", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "design", answer: "design", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "designer", answer: "suunnittelija", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "desire", answer: "himoita", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "desk", answer: "vastaanotto", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "desperate", answer: "epätoivoinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "despite", answer: "huolimatta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "destroy", answer: "tuhota", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "destruction", answer: "tuho", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "detail", answer: "yksityiskohta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "detailed", answer: "yksityiskohtainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "detect", answer: "havaita", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "determine", answer: "määrittää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "develop", answer: "kehittää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "developing", answer: "kehittämällä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "development", answer: "kehitys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "device", answer: "laite", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "devote", answer: "omistaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "dialogue", answer: "vuoropuhelu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "die", answer: "kuolla", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "diet", answer: "ruokavalio", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "differ", answer: "erota", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "difference", answer: "ero", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "different", answer: "eri", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "differently", answer: "eri tavalla", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "difficult", answer: "vaikea", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "difficulty", answer: "vaikeus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "dig", answer: "kaivaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "digital", answer: "digitaalinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "dimension", answer: "ulottuvuus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "dining", answer: "ruokailu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "dinner", answer: "päivällinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "direct", answer: "suoraan", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "direction", answer: "suunta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "directly", answer: "suoraan", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "director", answer: "johtaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "dirt", answer: "lika", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "dirty", answer: "likainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "disability", answer: "vammaisuus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "disagree", answer: "olla eri mieltä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "disappear", answer: "kadota", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "disaster", answer: "katastrofi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "discipline", answer: "kuri", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "discourse", answer: "esitelmä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "discover", answer: "tutustu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "discovery", answer: "löytö", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "discrimination", answer: "syrjintä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "discuss", answer: "keskustella", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "discussion", answer: "keskustelu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "disease", answer: "tauti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "dish", answer: "ruokalaji", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "dismiss", answer: "erottaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "disorder", answer: "häiriö", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "display", answer: "näyttö", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "dispute", answer: "riita", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "distance", answer: "etäisyys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "distant", answer: "kaukainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "distinct", answer: "selvä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "distinction", answer: "ero", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "distinguish", answer: "erottaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "distribute", answer: "jakaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "distribution", answer: "jakelu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "district", answer: "kaupunginosa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "diverse", answer: "monipuolinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "diversity", answer: "monimuotoisuus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "divide", answer: "jakaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "division", answer: "jako", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "divorce", answer: "avioero", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "dna", answer: "dna-", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "do", answer: "tehdä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "doctor", answer: "lääkäri", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "document", answer: "asiakirja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "dog", answer: "koira", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "domestic", answer: "kotimainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "dominant", answer: "hallitseva", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "dominate", answer: "hallitsevat", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "door", answer: "ovi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "double", answer: "kaksinkertainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "doubt", answer: "epäillä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "down", answer: "alas", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "downtown", answer: "keskustassa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "dozen", answer: "tusina", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "draft", answer: "laatia", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "drag", answer: "raahata", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "drama", answer: "draama", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "dramatic", answer: "dramaattinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "dramatically", answer: "dramaattisesti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "draw", answer: "piirtää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "drawing", answer: "piirustus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "dream", answer: "unelma", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "dress", answer: "mekko", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "drink", answer: "juoda", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "drive", answer: "ajaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "driver", answer: "kuljettaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "drop", answer: "pudota", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "drug", answer: "lääke", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "dry", answer: "kuiva", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "due", answer: "maksettava", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "during", answer: "aikana", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "dust", answer: "pöly", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "duty", answer: "velvollisuus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "each", answer: "kukin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "eager", answer: "innokas", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "ear", answer: "korva", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "early", answer: "aikaisin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "earn", answer: "ansaita", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "earnings", answer: "tulot", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "earth", answer: "maa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "ease", answer: "helppous", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "easily", answer: "helposti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "east", answer: "itään", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "eastern", answer: "itäinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "easy", answer: "helppo", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "eat", answer: "syödä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "economic", answer: "taloudellinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "economics", answer: "taloustiede", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "economist", answer: "taloustieteilijä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "economy", answer: "talous", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "edge", answer: "reuna", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "edition", answer: "painos", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "editor", answer: "toimittaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "educate", answer: "kouluttaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "education", answer: "koulutus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "educational", answer: "koulutuksellinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "educator", answer: "kasvattaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "effect", answer: "vaikutus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "effective", answer: "tehokas", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "effectively", answer: "tehokkaasti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "efficiency", answer: "tehokkuus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "efficient", answer: "tehokas", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "effort", answer: "ponnistus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "egg", answer: "kananmuna", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "eight", answer: "kahdeksan", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "either", answer: "jompikumpi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "elderly", answer: "vanhukset", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "elect", answer: "valita", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "election", answer: "vaalit", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "electric", answer: "sähköinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "electricity", answer: "sähkö", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "electronic", answer: "elektroninen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "element", answer: "elementti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "elementary", answer: "perus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "eliminate", answer: "poistaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "elite", answer: "eliitti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "else", answer: "muu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "elsewhere", answer: "muualla", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "e-mail", answer: "sähköposti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "embrace", answer: "omaksua", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "emerge", answer: "ilmaantua", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "emergency", answer: "hätä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "emission", answer: "päästö", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "emotion", answer: "tunne", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "emotional", answer: "tunteellinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "emphasis", answer: "painotus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "emphasize", answer: "painottaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "employ", answer: "käyttää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "employee", answer: "työntekijä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "employer", answer: "työnantaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "employment", answer: "työllisyys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "empty", answer: "tyhjä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "enable", answer: "ota käyttöön", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "encounter", answer: "kohdata", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "encourage", answer: "kannustaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "end", answer: "pää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "enemy", answer: "vihollinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "energy", answer: "energia", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "enforcement", answer: "täytäntöönpano", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "engage", answer: "sitoutua", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "engine", answer: "moottori", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "engineer", answer: "insinööri", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "engineering", answer: "tekniikka", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "english", answer: "englanti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "enhance", answer: "parantaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "enjoy", answer: "nauttia", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "enormous", answer: "valtava", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "enough", answer: "tarpeeksi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "ensure", answer: "varmistaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "enter", answer: "tulla sisään", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "enterprise", answer: "yritys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "entertainment", answer: "viihde", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "entire", answer: "koko", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "entirely", answer: "täysin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "entrance", answer: "sisäänkäynti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "entry", answer: "merkintä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "environment", answer: "ympäristö", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "environmental", answer: "ympäristö-", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "episode", answer: "episodi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "equal", answer: "yhtä suuri", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "equally", answer: "yhtä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "equipment", answer: "laitteet", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "era", answer: "aikakausi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "error", answer: "virhe", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "escape", answer: "paeta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "especially", answer: "erityisesti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "essay", answer: "essee", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "essential", answer: "olennainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "essentially", answer: "olennaisesti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "establish", answer: "perustaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "establishment", answer: "perustaminen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "estate", answer: "omaisuus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "estimate", answer: "arvio", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "etc", answer: "jne", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "ethics", answer: "etiikka", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "ethnic", answer: "etninen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "european", answer: "eurooppalainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "evaluate", answer: "arvioida", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "evaluation", answer: "arviointi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "even", answer: "jopa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "evening", answer: "ilta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "event", answer: "tapahtuma", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "eventually", answer: "lopulta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "ever", answer: "koskaan", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "every", answer: "joka", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "everybody", answer: "jokainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "everyday", answer: "joka päivä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "everyone", answer: "jokainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "everything", answer: "kaikki", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "everywhere", answer: "kaikkialla", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "evidence", answer: "näyttö", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "evolution", answer: "evoluutio", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "evolve", answer: "evolve", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "exact", answer: "tarkka", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "exactly", answer: "tarkalleen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "examination", answer: "tutkimus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "examine", answer: "tutkia", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "example", answer: "esimerkki", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "exceed", answer: "ylittää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "excellent", answer: "erinomainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "except", answer: "paitsi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "exception", answer: "poikkeus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "exchange", answer: "vaihto", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "exciting", answer: "jännittävä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "executive", answer: "johtaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "exercise", answer: "harjoittele", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "exhibit", answer: "näyttely", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "exhibition", answer: "näyttely", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "exist", answer: "olla olemassa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "existence", answer: "olemassaolo", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "existing", answer: "nykyinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "expand", answer: "laajentaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "expansion", answer: "laajeneminen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "expect", answer: "odottaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "expectation", answer: "odotus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "expense", answer: "kulu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "expensive", answer: "kallis", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "experience", answer: "kokea", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "experiment", answer: "koe", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "expert", answer: "asiantuntija", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "explain", answer: "selittää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "explanation", answer: "selitys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "explode", answer: "räjähtää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "explore", answer: "tutkia", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "explosion", answer: "räjähdys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "expose", answer: "paljastaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "exposure", answer: "valotus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "express", answer: "ilmaista", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "expression", answer: "ilmaisu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "extend", answer: "pidentää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "extension", answer: "laajentaminen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "extensive", answer: "laaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "extent", answer: "laajuus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "external", answer: "ulkoinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "extra", answer: "ylimääräinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "extraordinary", answer: "epätavallinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "extreme", answer: "äärimmäinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "extremely", answer: "erittäin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "eye", answer: "silmä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "fabric", answer: "kangas", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "face", answer: "kasvot", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "facility", answer: "laitos", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "fact", answer: "tosiasia", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "factor", answer: "tekijä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "factory", answer: "tehdas", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "faculty", answer: "henkilöstö", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "fade", answer: "häivyttää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "fail", answer: "fail", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "failure", answer: "vika", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "fair", answer: "oikeudenmukainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "fairly", answer: "melko", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "faith", answer: "usko", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "fall", answer: "pudota", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "false", answer: "väärä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "familiar", answer: "tuttu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "family", answer: "perhe", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "famous", answer: "kuuluisa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "fan", answer: "tuuletin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "fantasy", answer: "fantasia", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "far", answer: "pitkälle", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "farm", answer: "maatila", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "farmer", answer: "viljelijä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "fashion", answer: "muoti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "fast", answer: "nopeasti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "fat", answer: "rasva", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "fate", answer: "kohtalo", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "father", answer: "isä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "fault", answer: "vika", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "favor", answer: "hyväksi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "favorite", answer: "suosikki-", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "fear", answer: "pelko", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "feature", answer: "ominaisuus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "federal", answer: "liittovaltion-", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "fee", answer: "maksu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "feed", answer: "rehu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "feel", answer: "tuntea", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "feeling", answer: "tunne", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "fellow", answer: "kaveri", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "female", answer: "nainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "fence", answer: "aita", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "few", answer: "harvat", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "fewer", answer: "vähemmän", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "fiber", answer: "kuitu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "fiction", answer: "kaunokirjallisuus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "field", answer: "ala", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "fifteen", answer: "viisitoista", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "fifth", answer: "viides", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "fifty", answer: "viisikymmentä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "fight", answer: "taistella", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "fighter", answer: "taistelija", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "fighting", answer: "taistelevat", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "figure", answer: "kuva", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "file", answer: "tiedosto", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "fill", answer: "täyttää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "film", answer: "elokuva", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "final", answer: "lopullinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "finally", answer: "vihdoin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "finance", answer: "rahoittaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "financial", answer: "taloudellinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "find", answer: "löytö", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "finding", answer: "havainto", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "fine", answer: "hieno", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "finger", answer: "sormi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "finish", answer: "suorittaa loppuun", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "fire", answer: "antaa potkut", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "firm", answer: "yritys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "first", answer: "ensimmäinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "fish", answer: "kalastaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "fishing", answer: "kalastus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "fit", answer: "istuvuus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "fitness", answer: "kunto", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "five", answer: "viisi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "fix", answer: "korjata", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "flag", answer: "lippu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "flame", answer: "liekki", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "flat", answer: "tasainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "flavor", answer: "maku", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "flee", answer: "pakenemaan", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "flesh", answer: "liha", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "flight", answer: "lento", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "float", answer: "kellua", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "floor", answer: "lattia", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "flow", answer: "virtaus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "flower", answer: "kukka", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "fly", answer: "lentää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "focus", answer: "fokus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "folk", answer: "kansan-", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "follow", answer: "seurata", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "following", answer: "seurata", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "food", answer: "ruoka", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "foot", answer: "jalka", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "football", answer: "jalkapallo", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "for", answer: "varten", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "force", answer: "pakottaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "foreign", answer: "ulkomainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "forest", answer: "metsä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "forever", answer: "ikuisesti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "forget", answer: "unohtaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "form", answer: "muoto", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "formal", answer: "muodollinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "formation", answer: "muodostus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "former", answer: "entinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "formula", answer: "kaava", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "forth", answer: "eteenpäin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "fortune", answer: "onni", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "forward", answer: "eteenpäin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "found", answer: "löydetty", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "foundation", answer: "perusta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "founder", answer: "perustaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "four", answer: "neljä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "fourth", answer: "neljäs", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "frame", answer: "kehys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "framework", answer: "puitteet", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "free", answer: "vapaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "freedom", answer: "vapaus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "freeze", answer: "jäädyttää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "french", answer: "ranskan kieli", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "frequency", answer: "taajuus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "frequent", answer: "tiheä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "frequently", answer: "usein", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "fresh", answer: "tuore", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "friend", answer: "ystävä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "friendly", answer: "ystävällinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "friendship", answer: "ystävyys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "from", answer: "alkaen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "front", answer: "etuosa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "fruit", answer: "hedelmä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "frustration", answer: "pettymys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "fuel", answer: "polttoaine", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "full", answer: "koko", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "fully", answer: "täysin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "fun", answer: "hauska", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "function", answer: "toimia", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "fund", answer: "rahoittaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "fundamental", answer: "perus-", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "funding", answer: "rahoitus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "funeral", answer: "hautajaiset", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "funny", answer: "hauska", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "furniture", answer: "huonekalut", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "furthermore", answer: "lisäksi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "future", answer: "tulevaisuus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "gain", answer: "saada", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "galaxy", answer: "galaksi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "gallery", answer: "galleria", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "game", answer: "peli", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "gang", answer: "jengi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "gap", answer: "aukko", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "garage", answer: "autotalli", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "garden", answer: "puutarha", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "garlic", answer: "valkosipuli", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "gas", answer: "kaasu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "gate", answer: "portti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "gather", answer: "kerätä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "gay", answer: "homo", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "gaze", answer: "katse", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "gear", answer: "vaihde", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "gender", answer: "sukupuoli", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "gene", answer: "geeni", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "general", answer: "yleinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "generally", answer: "yleisesti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "generate", answer: "tuottaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "generation", answer: "sukupolvi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "genetic", answer: "geneettinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "gentleman", answer: "herrasmies", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "gently", answer: "kevyesti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "german", answer: "saksan kieli", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "gesture", answer: "ele", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "get", answer: "saada", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "ghost", answer: "aave", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "giant", answer: "jättiläinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "gift", answer: "lahja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "gifted", answer: "lahjakas", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "girl", answer: "tyttö", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "girlfriend", answer: "tyttöystävä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "give", answer: "antaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "given", answer: "tietty", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "glad", answer: "iloinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "glance", answer: "silmäys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "glass", answer: "lasi-", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "global", answer: "maailmanlaajuinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "glove", answer: "käsine", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "go", answer: "mennä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "goal", answer: "päämäärä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "god", answer: "jumala", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "gold", answer: "kulta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "golden", answer: "kultainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "golf", answer: "golf", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "good", answer: "hyvä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "government", answer: "hallitus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "governor", answer: "kuvernööri", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "grab", answer: "napata", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "grade", answer: "arvosana", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "gradually", answer: "vähitellen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "graduate", answer: "valmistua", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "grain", answer: "jyvä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "grand", answer: "suuri", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "grandfather", answer: "isoisä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "grandmother", answer: "isoäiti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "grant", answer: "myöntää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "grass", answer: "ruoho", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "grave", answer: "hauta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "gray", answer: "harmaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "great", answer: "loistava", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "greatest", answer: "suurin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "green", answer: "vihreä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "grocery", answer: "ruokakauppa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "ground", answer: "maa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "group", answer: "ryhmä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "grow", answer: "kasvaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "growing", answer: "kasvaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "growth", answer: "kasvu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "guarantee", answer: "takuu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "guard", answer: "vartija", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "guess", answer: "arvaus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "guest", answer: "vieras", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "guide", answer: "opas", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "guideline", answer: "ohje", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "guilty", answer: "syyllinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "gun", answer: "ase", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "guy", answer: "kaveri", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "habit", answer: "tottumus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "habitat", answer: "elinympäristö", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "hair", answer: "hiukset", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "half", answer: "puoli", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "hall", answer: "sali", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "hand", answer: "käsi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "handful", answer: "kourallinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "handle", answer: "käsitellä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "hang", answer: "roikkua", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "happen", answer: "tapahtua", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "happy", answer: "onnellinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "hard", answer: "kova", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "hardly", answer: "tuskin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "hat", answer: "hattu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "hate", answer: "viha", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "have", answer: "omistaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "he", answer: "hän", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "head", answer: "pää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "headline", answer: "otsikko", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "headquarters", answer: "päämaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "health", answer: "terveys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "healthy", answer: "terve", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "hear", answer: "kuulla", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "hearing", answer: "kuulo", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "heart", answer: "sydän", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "heat", answer: "lämpö", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "heaven", answer: "taivas", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "heavily", answer: "raskaasti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "heavy", answer: "raskas", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "heel", answer: "kantapää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "height", answer: "korkeus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "helicopter", answer: "helikopteri", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "hell", answer: "helvetti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "hello", answer: "hei", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "help", answer: "auta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "helpful", answer: "hyödyllinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "her", answer: "hänen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "here", answer: "tässä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "heritage", answer: "perintö", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "hero", answer: "sankari", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "herself", answer: "oma itsensä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "hey", answer: "hei", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "hi", answer: "moi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "hide", answer: "piilottaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "high", answer: "korkea", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "highlight", answer: "kohokohta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "highly", answer: "erittäin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "highway", answer: "valtatie", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "hill", answer: "mäki", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "him", answer: "häntä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "himself", answer: "hän itse", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "hip", answer: "lonkka", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "hire", answer: "vuokraus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "his", answer: "hänen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "historian", answer: "historioitsija", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "historic", answer: "historiallinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "historical", answer: "historiallinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "history", answer: "historia", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "hit", answer: "osuma", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "hold", answer: "hold", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "hole", answer: "reikä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "holiday", answer: "loma", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "holy", answer: "pyhä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "home", answer: "koti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "homeless", answer: "asunnoton", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "honest", answer: "rehellinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "honey", answer: "hunaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "honor", answer: "kunnia", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "hope", answer: "toivoa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "horizon", answer: "horisontti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "horror", answer: "kauhu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "horse", answer: "hevonen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "hospital", answer: "sairaala", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "host", answer: "isäntä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "hot", answer: "kuuma", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "hotel", answer: "hotelli", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "hour", answer: "tunnin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "house", answer: "talo", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "household", answer: "kotitalous", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "housing", answer: "kotelo", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "how", answer: "miten", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "however", answer: "kuitenkin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "huge", answer: "valtava", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "human", answer: "ihmisen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "humor", answer: "huumori", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "hundred", answer: "sata", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "hungry", answer: "nälkäinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "hunter", answer: "metsästäjä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "hunting", answer: "metsästys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "hurt", answer: "satuttaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "husband", answer: "aviomies", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "hypothesis", answer: "hypoteesi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "i", answer: "minä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "ice", answer: "jää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "idea", answer: "ajatus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "ideal", answer: "ihanteellinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "identification", answer: "henkilöllisyystodistus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "identify", answer: "tunnistaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "identity", answer: "identiteetti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "ie", answer: "eli", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "if", answer: "jos", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "ignore", answer: "jättää huomiotta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "ill", answer: "sairas", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "illegal", answer: "laiton", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "illness", answer: "sairaus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "illustrate", answer: "valaista", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "image", answer: "kuva", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "imagination", answer: "mielikuvitus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "imagine", answer: "kuvitella", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "immediate", answer: "välitön", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "immediately", answer: "heti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "immigrant", answer: "maahanmuuttaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "immigration", answer: "maahanmuutto", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "impact", answer: "vaikutus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "implement", answer: "toteuttaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "implication", answer: "seuraamus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "imply", answer: "vihjata", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "importance", answer: "merkitys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "important", answer: "tärkeä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "impose", answer: "määrätä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "impossible", answer: "mahdoton", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "impress", answer: "tehdä vaikutus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "impression", answer: "vaikutelma", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "impressive", answer: "vaikuttava", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "improve", answer: "parantaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "improvement", answer: "parannus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "in", answer: "sisään", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "incentive", answer: "kannustin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "incident", answer: "tapaus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "include", answer: "sisältää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "including", answer: "mukaan lukien", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "income", answer: "tulo", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "incorporate", answer: "sisällytä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "increase", answer: "lisääntyä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "increased", answer: "lisääntynyt", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "increasing", answer: "lisääntyy", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "increasingly", answer: "yhä useammin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "incredible", answer: "uskomaton", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "indeed", answer: "todellakin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "independence", answer: "itsenäisyys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "independent", answer: "itsenäinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "index", answer: "indeksi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "indian", answer: "intialainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "indicate", answer: "osoittaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "indication", answer: "osoitus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "individual", answer: "yksilö", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "industrial", answer: "teollinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "industry", answer: "ala", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "infant", answer: "pikkulasten", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "infection", answer: "infektio", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "inflation", answer: "inflaatio", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "influence", answer: "vaikutus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "inform", answer: "ilmoittaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "information", answer: "tiedot", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "ingredient", answer: "ainesosa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "initial", answer: "alkukirjain", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "initially", answer: "ensin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "initiative", answer: "aloite", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "injury", answer: "vahinko", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "inner", answer: "sisäinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "innocent", answer: "viaton", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "inquiry", answer: "tiedustelu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "inside", answer: "sisällä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "insight", answer: "oivallus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "insist", answer: "vaatia", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "inspire", answer: "innostaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "install", answer: "asentaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "instance", answer: "ilmentymä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "instead", answer: "sen sijaan", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "institution", answer: "instituutio", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "institutional", answer: "institutionaalinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "instruction", answer: "ohje", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "instructor", answer: "ohjaaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "instrument", answer: "väline", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "insurance", answer: "vakuutus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "intellectual", answer: "älyllinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "intelligence", answer: "älykkyys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "intend", answer: "aikovat", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "intense", answer: "voimakas", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "intensity", answer: "intensiteetti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "intention", answer: "tarkoitus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "interaction", answer: "vuorovaikutus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "interest", answer: "kiinnostuksen kohde", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "interested", answer: "kiinnostunut", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "interesting", answer: "mielenkiintoista", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "internal", answer: "sisäinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "international", answer: "kansainvälinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "internet", answer: "internet", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "interpret", answer: "tulkita", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "interpretation", answer: "tulkinta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "intervention", answer: "interventio", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "interview", answer: "haastatella", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "into", answer: "osaksi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "introduce", answer: "esitellä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "introduction", answer: "esittely", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "invasion", answer: "maahantunkeutuminen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "invest", answer: "sijoittaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "investigate", answer: "tutkia", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "investigation", answer: "tutkimus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "investigator", answer: "tutkija", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "investment", answer: "investointi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "investor", answer: "sijoittaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "invite", answer: "kutsu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "involve", answer: "sisältää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "involved", answer: "mukana", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "involvement", answer: "osallistuminen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "iraqi", answer: "irakilainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "irish", answer: "irlantilainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "iron", answer: "rauta-", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "islamic", answer: "islamilainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "island", answer: "saari", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "israeli", answer: "israelilainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "issue", answer: "ongelma", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "it", answer: "se", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "italian", answer: "italialainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "item", answer: "erä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "its", answer: "sen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "itself", answer: "itse", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "jacket", answer: "takki", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "jail", answer: "vankila", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "japanese", answer: "japanilainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "jet", answer: "suihkukone", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "jew", answer: "juutalainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "jewish", answer: "juutalainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "job", answer: "job", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "join", answer: "liittyä seuraan", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "joint", answer: "yhteinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "joke", answer: "vitsi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "journal", answer: "päiväkirja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "journalist", answer: "toimittaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "journey", answer: "matka", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "joy", answer: "ilo", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "judge", answer: "tuomari", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "judgment", answer: "tuomio", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "juice", answer: "mehu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "jump", answer: "hypätä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "junior", answer: "nuorempi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "jury", answer: "tuomaristo", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "just", answer: "vain", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "justice", answer: "oikeudenmukaisuus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "justify", answer: "perustella", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "keep", answer: "pitää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "key", answer: "avain", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "kick", answer: "potkia", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "kid", answer: "lapsi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "kill", answer: "tappaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "killer", answer: "tappaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "killing", answer: "tappaminen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "kind", answer: "kiltti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "king", answer: "kuningas", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "kiss", answer: "suudella", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "kitchen", answer: "keittiö", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "knee", answer: "polvi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "knife", answer: "veitsi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "knock", answer: "koputtaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "know", answer: "tietää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "knowledge", answer: "tuntemus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "lab", answer: "laboratorio", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "label", answer: "etiketti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "labor", answer: "työvoima", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "laboratory", answer: "laboratorio", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "lack", answer: "puute", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "lady", answer: "nainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "lake", answer: "järvi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "land", answer: "maa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "landscape", answer: "maisema", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "language", answer: "kieli", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "lap", answer: "kierros", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "large", answer: "suuri", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "largely", answer: "enimmäkseen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "last", answer: "kestää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "late", answer: "myöhään", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "later", answer: "myöhemmin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "latin", answer: "latina", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "latter", answer: "jälkimmäinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "laugh", answer: "nauraa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "launch", answer: "tuoda markkinoille", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "law", answer: "laki", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "lawn", answer: "nurmikko", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "lawsuit", answer: "oikeusjuttu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "lawyer", answer: "lakimies", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "lay", answer: "lay", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "layer", answer: "kerros", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "lead", answer: "johtaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "leader", answer: "johtaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "leadership", answer: "johto", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "leading", answer: "johtava", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "leaf", answer: "puun lehti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "league", answer: "liiga", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "lean", answer: "nojata", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "learn", answer: "oppia", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "learning", answer: "oppiminen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "least", answer: "vähiten", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "leather", answer: "nahka", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "leave", answer: "leave", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "left", answer: "vasen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "leg", answer: "jalka", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "legacy", answer: "perintö", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "legal", answer: "oikeudellinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "legend", answer: "legenda", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "legislation", answer: "lainsäädäntö", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "legitimate", answer: "laillinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "lemon", answer: "sitruuna", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "length", answer: "pituus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "less", answer: "vähemmän", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "lesson", answer: "oppitunti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "let", answer: "antaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "letter", answer: "kirjain", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "level", answer: "taso", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "liberal", answer: "liberaali", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "library", answer: "kirjasto", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "license", answer: "lisenssi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "lie", answer: "valehdella", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "life", answer: "elämä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "lifestyle", answer: "elämäntapa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "lifetime", answer: "elinikä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "lift", answer: "hissi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "light", answer: "valo", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "like", answer: "kuten", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "likely", answer: "todennäköisesti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "limit", answer: "raja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "limitation", answer: "rajoitus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "limited", answer: "rajallinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "line", answer: "linja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "link", answer: "linkki", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "lip", answer: "huuli", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "list", answer: "lista", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "listen", answer: "kuunnella", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "literally", answer: "kirjaimellisesti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "literary", answer: "kirjallisuuden-", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "literature", answer: "kirjallisuus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "little", answer: "vähän", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "live", answer: "elää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "living", answer: "elävä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "load", answer: "ladata", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "loan", answer: "lainata", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "local", answer: "paikallinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "locate", answer: "paikantaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "location", answer: "sijainti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "lock", answer: "lukko", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "long", answer: "pitkä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "long-term", answer: "pitkäaikainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "look", answer: "katso", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "loose", answer: "löysä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "lose", answer: "menettää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "loss", answer: "menetys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "lost", answer: "menetetty", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "lot", answer: "erä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "lots", answer: "paljon", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "loud", answer: "äänekäs", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "love", answer: "rakkaus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "lovely", answer: "ihana", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "lover", answer: "rakastaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "low", answer: "matala", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "lower", answer: "alempi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "luck", answer: "onni", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "lucky", answer: "onnekas", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "lunch", answer: "lounas", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "lung", answer: "keuhko", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "machine", answer: "kone", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "mad", answer: "vihainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "magazine", answer: "aikakauslehti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "mail", answer: "posti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "main", answer: "tärkein", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "mainly", answer: "pääosin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "maintain", answer: "ylläpitää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "maintenance", answer: "ylläpito", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "major", answer: "suuri", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "majority", answer: "suurin osa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "make", answer: "tehdä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "maker", answer: "luoja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "makeup", answer: "meikki", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "male", answer: "uros", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "mall", answer: "ostoskeskus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "man", answer: "mies", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "manage", answer: "hoitaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "management", answer: "johto", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "manager", answer: "johtaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "manner", answer: "tapa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "manufacturer", answer: "valmistaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "manufacturing", answer: "valmistus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "many", answer: "monet", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "map", answer: "kartta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "margin", answer: "marginaali", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "mark", answer: "merkki", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "market", answer: "markkinoida", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "marketing", answer: "markkinointi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "marriage", answer: "avioliitto", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "married", answer: "naimisissa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "marry", answer: "naida", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "mask", answer: "naamio", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "mass", answer: "massa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "massive", answer: "massiivinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "master", answer: "hallita", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "match", answer: "ottelu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "material", answer: "materiaali", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "math", answer: "matematiikka", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "matter", answer: "asia", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "may", answer: "saattaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "maybe", answer: "voi olla", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "mayor", answer: "pormestari", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "me", answer: "minä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "meal", answer: "ateria", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "mean", answer: "tarkoittaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "meaning", answer: "merkitys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "meanwhile", answer: "sillä välin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "measure", answer: "mitata", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "measurement", answer: "mittaus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "meat", answer: "liha", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "mechanism", answer: "mekanismi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "media", answer: "tiedotusvälineet", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "medical", answer: "lääketieteellinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "medication", answer: "lääkitys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "medicine", answer: "lääketiede", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "medium", answer: "keskikokoinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "meet", answer: "tavata", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "meeting", answer: "tapaaminen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "member", answer: "jäsen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "membership", answer: "jäsenyys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "memory", answer: "muisti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "mental", answer: "henkinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "mention", answer: "mainita", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "menu", answer: "valikko", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "mere", answer: "pelkkä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "merely", answer: "vain", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "mess", answer: "sotku", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "message", answer: "viesti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "metal", answer: "metalli-", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "meter", answer: "mittari", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "method", answer: "menetelmä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "mexican", answer: "meksikolainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "middle", answer: "keskimmäinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "might", answer: "voimin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "military", answer: "sotilaallinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "milk", answer: "maito", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "million", answer: "miljoona", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "mind", answer: "mieli", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "mine", answer: "kaivos", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "minister", answer: "ministeri", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "minor", answer: "vähäinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "minority", answer: "vähemmistö", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "minute", answer: "minuutti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "miracle", answer: "ihme", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "mirror", answer: "peili", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "miss", answer: "neiti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "missile", answer: "ohjus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "mission", answer: "tehtävä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "mistake", answer: "virhe", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "mix", answer: "mix", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "mixture", answer: "seos", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "mm-hmm", answer: "mm-hmm", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "mode", answer: "tila", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "model", answer: "malli", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "moderate", answer: "kohtalainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "modern", answer: "moderni", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "modest", answer: "vaatimaton", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "mom", answer: "äiti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "moment", answer: "hetki", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "money", answer: "raha", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "monitor", answer: "monitori", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "month", answer: "kuukausi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "mood", answer: "mieliala", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "moon", answer: "kuu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "moral", answer: "moraalinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "more", answer: "lisää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "moreover", answer: "lisäksi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "morning", answer: "aamu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "mortgage", answer: "kiinnitys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "most", answer: "useimmat", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "mostly", answer: "enimmäkseen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "mother", answer: "äiti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "motion", answer: "liike", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "motivation", answer: "motivaatio", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "motor", answer: "moottori", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "mount", answer: "asentaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "mountain", answer: "vuori", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "mouse", answer: "hiiri", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "mouth", answer: "suu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "move", answer: "liikkua", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "movement", answer: "liike", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "movie", answer: "elokuva", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "mr", answer: "herra", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "mrs", answer: "rouva", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "ms", answer: "neiti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "much", answer: "paljon", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "multiple", answer: "moninkertainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "murder", answer: "murhata", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "muscle", answer: "lihas", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "museum", answer: "museo", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "music", answer: "musiikki", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "musical", answer: "musikaali", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "musician", answer: "muusikko", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "muslim", answer: "muslimi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "must", answer: "on pakko", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "mutual", answer: "keskinäinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "my", answer: "minun", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "myself", answer: "itse", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "mystery", answer: "mysteeri", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "myth", answer: "myytti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "naked", answer: "alasti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "name", answer: "nimi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "narrative", answer: "kerronta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "narrow", answer: "kapea", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "nation", answer: "kansakunta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "national", answer: "kansallinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "native", answer: "syntyperäinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "natural", answer: "luonnollinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "naturally", answer: "luonnollisesti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "nature", answer: "luonto", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "near", answer: "lähellä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "nearby", answer: "lähistöllä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "nearly", answer: "lähes", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "necessarily", answer: "välttämättä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "necessary", answer: "välttämätön", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "neck", answer: "niska", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "need", answer: "tarve", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "negative", answer: "negatiivinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "negotiate", answer: "neuvotella", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "negotiation", answer: "neuvottelu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "neighbor", answer: "naapuri", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "neighborhood", answer: "naapuruus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "neither", answer: "ei kumpikaan", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "nerve", answer: "hermo", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "nervous", answer: "hermostunut", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "net", answer: "netto", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "network", answer: "verkko", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "never", answer: "ei koskaan", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "nevertheless", answer: "tästä huolimatta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "new", answer: "uusi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "newly", answer: "hiljattain", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "news", answer: "uutiset", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "newspaper", answer: "sanomalehti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "next", answer: "seuraava", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "nice", answer: "kiva", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "night", answer: "yö", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "nine", answer: "yhdeksän", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "no", answer: "ei", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "nobody", answer: "ei kukaan", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "nod", answer: "nyökkäys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "noise", answer: "melu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "nomination", answer: "nimitys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "none", answer: "ei mitään", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "nonetheless", answer: "kuitenkin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "nor", answer: "ei myöskään", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "normal", answer: "normaali", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "normally", answer: "yleensä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "north", answer: "pohjoinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "northern", answer: "pohjoinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "nose", answer: "nenä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "not", answer: "ei", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "note", answer: "huomautus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "nothing", answer: "ei mitään", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "notice", answer: "ilmoitus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "notion", answer: "käsite", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "novel", answer: "uusi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "now", answer: "nyt", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "nowhere", answer: "ei missään", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "nt", answer: "ei", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "nuclear", answer: "ydin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "number", answer: "määrä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "numerous", answer: "useat", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "nurse", answer: "sairaanhoitaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "nut", answer: "mutteri", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "object", answer: "esine", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "objective", answer: "tavoite", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "obligation", answer: "vaatimus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "observation", answer: "havainto", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "observe", answer: "tarkkailla", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "observer", answer: "tarkkailija", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "obtain", answer: "saada", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "obvious", answer: "ilmeinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "obviously", answer: "ilmeisesti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "occasion", answer: "tilaisuus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "occasionally", answer: "silloin tällöin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "occupation", answer: "ammatti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "occupy", answer: "miehittää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "occur", answer: "tapahtua", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "ocean", answer: "valtameri", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "odd", answer: "outo", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "odds", answer: "todennäköisyys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "of", answer: "of", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "off", answer: "vinossa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "offense", answer: "rikkomus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "offensive", answer: "loukkaava", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "offer", answer: "tarjous", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "office", answer: "toimisto", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "officer", answer: "upseeri", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "official", answer: "virallinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "often", answer: "usein", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "oh", answer: "vai niin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "oil", answer: "öljy", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "ok", answer: "kunnossa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "okay", answer: "okei", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "old", answer: "vanha", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "olympic", answer: "olympia-", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "on", answer: "päällä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "once", answer: "kerran", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "one", answer: "yksi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "ongoing", answer: "meneillään oleva", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "onion", answer: "sipuli", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "online", answer: "verkossa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "only", answer: "vain", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "onto", answer: "päälle", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "open", answer: "avata", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "opening", answer: "aukko", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "operate", answer: "toimia", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "operating", answer: "käyttö-", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "operation", answer: "operaatio", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "operator", answer: "operaattori", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "opinion", answer: "lausunto", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "opponent", answer: "vastustaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "opportunity", answer: "tilaisuus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "oppose", answer: "vastustaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "opposite", answer: "vastapäätä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "opposition", answer: "oppositio", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "option", answer: "vaihtoehto", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "or", answer: "tai", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "orange", answer: "oranssi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "order", answer: "tilaus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "ordinary", answer: "tavallinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "organic", answer: "luomu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "organization", answer: "organisaatio", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "organize", answer: "järjestää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "orientation", answer: "suuntautuminen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "origin", answer: "alkuperä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "original", answer: "alkuperäinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "originally", answer: "alun perin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "other", answer: "muut", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "others", answer: "toiset", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "otherwise", answer: "muuten", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "ought", answer: "pitäisi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "our", answer: "meidän", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "ourselves", answer: "itse", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "out", answer: "ulos", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "outcome", answer: "tulokset", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "outside", answer: "ulkopuolella", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "oven", answer: "uuni", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "over", answer: "yli", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "overall", answer: "yleensä ottaen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "overcome", answer: "voittaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "overlook", answer: "unohtaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "owe", answer: "olla velkaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "own", answer: "oma", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "owner", answer: "omistaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "pace", answer: "vauhti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "pack", answer: "pakkaus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "package", answer: "paketti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "page", answer: "sivu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "pain", answer: "kipu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "painful", answer: "tuskallinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "paint", answer: "maali-", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "painter", answer: "taidemaalari", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "painting", answer: "maalaus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "pair", answer: "pari", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "pale", answer: "kalpea", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "palestinian", answer: "palestiinalainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "palm", answer: "palmu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "pan", answer: "panoroida", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "panel", answer: "paneeli", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "pant", answer: "huohottaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "paper", answer: "paperi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "parent", answer: "vanhempi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "park", answer: "pysäköidä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "parking", answer: "pysäköinti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "part", answer: "osa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "participant", answer: "osallistuja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "participate", answer: "osallistua", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "participation", answer: "osallistumista", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "particular", answer: "tietty", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "particularly", answer: "erityisesti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "partly", answer: "osittain", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "partner", answer: "kumppani", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "partnership", answer: "kumppanuus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "party", answer: "juhla", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "pass", answer: "kulkea", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "passage", answer: "kulku", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "passenger", answer: "matkustaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "passion", answer: "intohimo", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "past", answer: "menneisyys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "patch", answer: "läikkä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "path", answer: "polku", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "patient", answer: "potilas", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "pattern", answer: "kuvio", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "pause", answer: "tauko", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "pay", answer: "maksaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "payment", answer: "maksu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "pc", answer: "pc", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "peace", answer: "rauha", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "peak", answer: "huippu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "peer", answer: "tähyillä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "penalty", answer: "rangaistus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "people", answer: "ihmiset", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "pepper", answer: "pippuri", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "per", answer: "kohti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "perceive", answer: "hahmottaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "percentage", answer: "prosenttimäärä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "perception", answer: "havaintokyky", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "perfect", answer: "täydellinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "perfectly", answer: "täydellisesti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "perform", answer: "suorittaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "performance", answer: "esitys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "perhaps", answer: "kenties", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "period", answer: "aika", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "permanent", answer: "pysyvä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "permission", answer: "lupa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "permit", answer: "lupa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "person", answer: "henkilö", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "personal", answer: "henkilökohtainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "personality", answer: "persoonallisuus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "personally", answer: "henkilökohtaisesti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "personnel", answer: "henkilöstö", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "perspective", answer: "näkökulma", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "persuade", answer: "suostutella", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "pet", answer: "lemmikki", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "phase", answer: "vaihe", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "phenomenon", answer: "ilmiö", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "philosophy", answer: "filosofia", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "phone", answer: "puhelin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "photo", answer: "kuva", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "photograph", answer: "valokuva", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "photographer", answer: "valokuvaaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "phrase", answer: "fraasi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "physical", answer: "fyysinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "physically", answer: "fyysisesti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "physician", answer: "lääkäri", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "piano", answer: "piano", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "pick", answer: "valita", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "picture", answer: "kuva", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "pie", answer: "piirakka", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "piece", answer: "pala", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "pile", answer: "pino", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "pilot", answer: "lentäjä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "pine", answer: "mänty", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "pink", answer: "pinkki", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "pipe", answer: "putki", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "pitch", answer: "piki", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "place", answer: "paikka", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "plan", answer: "suunnitelma", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "plane", answer: "kone", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "planet", answer: "planeetta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "planning", answer: "suunnittelu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "plant", answer: "tehdas", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "plastic", answer: "muovi-", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "plate", answer: "lautanen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "platform", answer: "foorumi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "play", answer: "pelata", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "player", answer: "pelaaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "please", answer: "ole kiltti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "pleasure", answer: "ilo", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "plenty", answer: "paljon", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "plot", answer: "juoni", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "plus", answer: "plus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "pm", answer: "pääministeri", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "pocket", answer: "tasku", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "poem", answer: "runo", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "poet", answer: "runoilija", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "poetry", answer: "runous", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "point", answer: "kohta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "pole", answer: "napa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "police", answer: "poliisi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "policy", answer: "käytäntö", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "political", answer: "poliittinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "politically", answer: "poliittisesti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "politician", answer: "poliitikko", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "politics", answer: "politiikka", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "poll", answer: "äänestys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "pollution", answer: "saastuminen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "pool", answer: "pool", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "poor", answer: "huono", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "pop", answer: "pop-", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "popular", answer: "suosittu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "population", answer: "väestö", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "porch", answer: "kuisti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "port", answer: "portti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "portion", answer: "osa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "portrait", answer: "muotokuva", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "portray", answer: "kuvata", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "pose", answer: "aiheuttaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "position", answer: "asento", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "positive", answer: "positiivinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "possess", answer: "omistaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "possibility", answer: "mahdollisuus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "possible", answer: "mahdollinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "possibly", answer: "mahdollisesti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "post", answer: "lähettää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "pot", answer: "pannu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "potato", answer: "peruna", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "potential", answer: "mahdollinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "potentially", answer: "mahdollisesti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "pound", answer: "punta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "pour", answer: "kaataa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "poverty", answer: "köyhyys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "powder", answer: "jauhe", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "power", answer: "teho", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "powerful", answer: "voimakas", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "practical", answer: "käytännöllinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "practice", answer: "harjoitella", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "pray", answer: "rukoilla", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "prayer", answer: "rukous", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "precisely", answer: "tarkasti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "predict", answer: "ennustaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "prefer", answer: "mieluummin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "preference", answer: "etusija", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "pregnancy", answer: "raskaus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "pregnant", answer: "raskaana", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "preparation", answer: "valmistautuminen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "prepare", answer: "valmistella", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "prescription", answer: "resepti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "presence", answer: "läsnäolo", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "present", answer: "esittää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "presentation", answer: "esittely", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "preserve", answer: "suojella", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "president", answer: "presidentti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "presidential", answer: "presidentin-", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "press", answer: "lehdistö", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "pressure", answer: "paine", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "pretend", answer: "teeskennellä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "pretty", answer: "nätti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "prevent", answer: "estää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "previous", answer: "edellinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "previously", answer: "aiemmin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "price", answer: "hinta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "pride", answer: "ylpeys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "priest", answer: "pappi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "primarily", answer: "pääasiallisesti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "primary", answer: "ensisijainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "prime", answer: "tärkein", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "principal", answer: "pääasiallinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "principle", answer: "periaate", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "print", answer: "tulosta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "prior", answer: "ennen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "priority", answer: "prioriteetti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "prison", answer: "vankila", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "prisoner", answer: "vanki", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "privacy", answer: "yksityisyys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "private", answer: "yksityinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "probably", answer: "todennäköisesti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "problem", answer: "ongelma", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "procedure", answer: "menettely", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "proceed", answer: "edetä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "process", answer: "käsitellä asiaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "produce", answer: "tuottaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "producer", answer: "tuottaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "product", answer: "tuote", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "production", answer: "tuotanto", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "profession", answer: "ammatti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "professional", answer: "ammattilainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "professor", answer: "professori", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "profile", answer: "profiili", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "profit", answer: "voitto", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "program", answer: "ohjelmoida", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "progress", answer: "edistyminen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "project", answer: "projekti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "prominent", answer: "näkyvä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "promise", answer: "lupaus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "promote", answer: "edistää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "prompt", answer: "nopea", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "proof", answer: "todiste", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "proper", answer: "asianmukainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "properly", answer: "oikein", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "property", answer: "omaisuus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "proportion", answer: "osa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "proposal", answer: "ehdotus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "propose", answer: "ehdottaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "proposed", answer: "ehdotettu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "prosecutor", answer: "syyttäjä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "prospect", answer: "näkymä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "protect", answer: "suojella", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "protection", answer: "suojaus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "protein", answer: "proteiini", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "protest", answer: "protesti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "proud", answer: "ylpeä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "prove", answer: "todistaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "provide", answer: "säätää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "provider", answer: "toimittaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "province", answer: "maakunta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "provision", answer: "säännös", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "psychological", answer: "psykologinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "psychologist", answer: "psykologi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "psychology", answer: "psykologia", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "public", answer: "julkinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "publication", answer: "julkaisu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "publicly", answer: "julkisesti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "publish", answer: "julkaista", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "publisher", answer: "kustantaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "pull", answer: "vedä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "punishment", answer: "rankaiseminen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "purchase", answer: "ostaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "pure", answer: "puhdas", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "purpose", answer: "tarkoitus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "pursue", answer: "jatkaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "push", answer: "työntää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "put", answer: "laittaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "qualify", answer: "pätevöityä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "quality", answer: "laatu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "quarter", answer: "neljännes", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "quarterback", answer: "pelinrakentaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "question", answer: "kysymys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "quick", answer: "nopea", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "quickly", answer: "nopeasti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "quiet", answer: "hiljainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "quietly", answer: "hiljaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "quit", answer: "lopettaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "quite", answer: "melko", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "quote", answer: "lainata", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "race", answer: "rotu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "racial", answer: "rodullinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "radical", answer: "radikaali", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "radio", answer: "radio", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "rail", answer: "kisko", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "rain", answer: "sade", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "raise", answer: "nostaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "range", answer: "alue", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "rank", answer: "arvo", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "rapid", answer: "nopea", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "rapidly", answer: "nopeasti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "rare", answer: "harvinainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "rarely", answer: "harvoin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "rate", answer: "nopeus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "rather", answer: "pikemminkin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "rating", answer: "luokitus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "ratio", answer: "suhde", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "raw", answer: "raaka", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "reach", answer: "saavuttaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "react", answer: "suhtautua", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "reaction", answer: "reaktio", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "read", answer: "lukea", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "reader", answer: "lukija", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "reading", answer: "lukeminen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "ready", answer: "valmis", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "real", answer: "todellinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "reality", answer: "todellisuus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "realize", answer: "realize", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "really", answer: "todella", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "reason", answer: "syy", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "reasonable", answer: "kohtuullinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "recall", answer: "palauttaa mieleen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "receive", answer: "vastaanottaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "recent", answer: "viimeaikainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "recently", answer: "äskettäin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "recipe", answer: "resepti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "recognition", answer: "tunnustus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "recognize", answer: "tunnistaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "recommend", answer: "suositella", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "recommendation", answer: "suositus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "record", answer: "ennätys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "recording", answer: "äänite", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "recover", answer: "toipua", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "recovery", answer: "elpyminen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "recruit", answer: "rekrytoida", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "red", answer: "punainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "reduce", answer: "vähentää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "reduction", answer: "vähentäminen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "refer", answer: "viitata", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "reference", answer: "viite", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "reflect", answer: "heijastaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "reflection", answer: "heijastus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "reform", answer: "uudistaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "refugee", answer: "pakolainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "refuse", answer: "kieltäytyä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "regard", answer: "ottaa huomioon", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "regarding", answer: "suhteen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "regardless", answer: "riippumatta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "regime", answer: "järjestelmä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "region", answer: "alue", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "regional", answer: "alueellinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "register", answer: "ilmoittautua", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "regular", answer: "säännöllinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "regularly", answer: "säännöllisesti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "regulate", answer: "säännellä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "regulation", answer: "säätö", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "reinforce", answer: "vahvistaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "reject", answer: "hylätä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "relate", answer: "koskea", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "relation", answer: "suhde", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "relationship", answer: "yhteys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "relative", answer: "suhteellinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "relatively", answer: "suhteellisesti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "relax", answer: "rentoutua", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "release", answer: "julkaisu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "relevant", answer: "merkityksellinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "relief", answer: "helpotus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "religion", answer: "uskonto", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "religious", answer: "uskonnollinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "rely", answer: "luottaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "remain", answer: "jäädä jäljelle", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "remaining", answer: "jäljelle jäänyt", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "remarkable", answer: "huomattava", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "remember", answer: "muistaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "remind", answer: "muistuttaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "remote", answer: "etä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "remove", answer: "poista", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "repeat", answer: "toistaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "repeatedly", answer: "toistuvasti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "replace", answer: "korvata", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "reply", answer: "vastaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "report", answer: "raportti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "reporter", answer: "reportteri", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "represent", answer: "edustaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "representation", answer: "edustus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "representative", answer: "edustaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "republican", answer: "tasavaltalainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "reputation", answer: "maine", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "request", answer: "pyyntö", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "require", answer: "vaatia", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "requirement", answer: "vaatimus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "research", answer: "tutkimus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "researcher", answer: "tutkija", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "resemble", answer: "muistuttaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "reservation", answer: "varaus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "resident", answer: "asukas", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "resist", answer: "vastustaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "resistance", answer: "vastus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "resolution", answer: "päätöslauselma", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "resolve", answer: "ratkaista", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "resort", answer: "turvautua", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "resource", answer: "resurssi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "respect", answer: "kunnioittaminen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "respond", answer: "vastata", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "respondent", answer: "vastaaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "response", answer: "vastaus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "responsibility", answer: "vastuu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "responsible", answer: "vastuullinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "rest", answer: "levätä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "restaurant", answer: "ravintola", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "restore", answer: "palauttaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "restriction", answer: "rajoitus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "result", answer: "tulos", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "retain", answer: "säilyttää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "retire", answer: "jäädä eläkkeelle", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "retirement", answer: "eläke", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "return", answer: "palata", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "reveal", answer: "paljastaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "revenue", answer: "tulot", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "review", answer: "arvostelu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "revolution", answer: "vallankumous", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "rhythm", answer: "rytmi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "rice", answer: "riisi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "rich", answer: "rikas", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "rid", answer: "eroon", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "ride", answer: "ratsastaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "rifle", answer: "kivääri", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "right", answer: "oikea", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "ring", answer: "rengas", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "rise", answer: "kohota", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "risk", answer: "riski", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "river", answer: "joki", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "road", answer: "tie", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "rock", answer: "rock", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "role", answer: "rooli", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "roll", answer: "rulla", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "romantic", answer: "romanttinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "roof", answer: "katto", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "room", answer: "huone", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "root", answer: "juuri", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "rope", answer: "köysi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "rose", answer: "ruusu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "rough", answer: "karkea", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "roughly", answer: "karkeasti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "round", answer: "pyöristää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "route", answer: "reitti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "routine", answer: "rutiini", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "row", answer: "rivi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "rub", answer: "hieroa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "rule", answer: "sääntö", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "run", answer: "juosta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "running", answer: "käynnissä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "rural", answer: "maaseudun", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "rush", answer: "kiire", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "russian", answer: "venäjän kieli", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "sacred", answer: "pyhä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "sad", answer: "surullinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "safe", answer: "turvallinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "safety", answer: "turvallisuus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "sake", answer: "vuoksi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "salad", answer: "salaatti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "salary", answer: "palkkaus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "sale", answer: "myynti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "sales", answer: "myynti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "salt", answer: "suola", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "same", answer: "sama", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "sample", answer: "näyte", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "sanction", answer: "sanktio", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "sand", answer: "hiekka", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "satellite", answer: "satelliitti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "satisfaction", answer: "tyytyväisyys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "satisfy", answer: "täyttää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "sauce", answer: "kastike", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "save", answer: "tallentaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "saving", answer: "tallentaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "say", answer: "sanoa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "scale", answer: "asteikko", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "scandal", answer: "skandaali", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "scared", answer: "pelottaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "scenario", answer: "skenaario", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "scene", answer: "näkymä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "schedule", answer: "ajoittaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "scheme", answer: "ohjelma", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "scholar", answer: "tutkija", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "scholarship", answer: "apuraha", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "school", answer: "koulu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "science", answer: "tiede", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "scientific", answer: "tieteellinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "scientist", answer: "tiedemies", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "scope", answer: "laajuus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "score", answer: "pisteet", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "scream", answer: "huutaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "screen", answer: "kuvaruutu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "script", answer: "käsikirjoitus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "sea", answer: "meri", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "search", answer: "hae", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "season", answer: "kausi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "seat", answer: "istuin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "second", answer: "toinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "secret", answer: "salaisuus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "secretary", answer: "sihteeri", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "section", answer: "jakso", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "sector", answer: "sektori", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "secure", answer: "turvallinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "security", answer: "turvallisuus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "see", answer: "nähdä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "seed", answer: "siemen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "seek", answer: "etsiä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "seem", answer: "näyttää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "segment", answer: "segmentti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "seize", answer: "takavarikoida", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "select", answer: "valita", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "selection", answer: "valinta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "self", answer: "itse", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "sell", answer: "myydä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "senate", answer: "senaatti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "senator", answer: "senaattori", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "send", answer: "lähettää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "senior", answer: "vanhempi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "sense", answer: "tunne", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "sensitive", answer: "herkkä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "sentence", answer: "tuomita", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "separate", answer: "erillinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "sequence", answer: "jakso", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "series", answer: "sarja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "serious", answer: "vakava", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "seriously", answer: "vakavasti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "serve", answer: "palvella", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "service", answer: "palvelu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "session", answer: "istunto", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "set", answer: "aseta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "setting", answer: "asetus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "settle", answer: "laskeutua", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "settlement", answer: "tilitys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "seven", answer: "seitsemän", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "several", answer: "useat", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "severe", answer: "vakava", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "sex", answer: "sukupuoli", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "sexual", answer: "seksuaalinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "shade", answer: "sävy", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "shadow", answer: "varjo", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "shake", answer: "ravistaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "shall", answer: "on", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "shape", answer: "muoto", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "share", answer: "jaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "sharp", answer: "terävä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "she", answer: "hän", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "sheet", answer: "arkki", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "shelf", answer: "hylly", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "shell", answer: "kuori", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "shelter", answer: "suoja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "shift", answer: "siirtää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "shine", answer: "paistaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "ship", answer: "alus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "shirt", answer: "paita", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "shit", answer: "paska", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "shock", answer: "shokki", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "shoe", answer: "kenkä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "shoot", answer: "ampua", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "shooting", answer: "ammunta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "shop", answer: "myymälä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "shopping", answer: "ostokset", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "shore", answer: "ranta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "short", answer: "lyhyt", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "shortly", answer: "pian", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "shot", answer: "laukaus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "should", answer: "pitäisi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "shoulder", answer: "olka", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "shout", answer: "huutaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "show", answer: "näytä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "shower", answer: "suihku", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "shrug", answer: "olankohautus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "shut", answer: "sulkea", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "sick", answer: "sairas", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "side", answer: "puoli", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "sigh", answer: "huokaus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "sight", answer: "näky", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "sign", answer: "merkki", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "signal", answer: "signaali", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "significance", answer: "merkitys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "significant", answer: "merkittävä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "significantly", answer: "merkittävästi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "silence", answer: "hiljaisuus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "silent", answer: "hiljainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "silver", answer: "hopea", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "similar", answer: "samankaltainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "similarly", answer: "samalla lailla", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "simple", answer: "yksinkertainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "simply", answer: "yksinkertaisesti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "sin", answer: "synti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "since", answer: "siitä asti kun", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "sing", answer: "laulaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "singer", answer: "laulaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "single", answer: "yksittäinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "sink", answer: "pesuallas", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "sir", answer: "arvon herra", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "sister", answer: "sisko", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "sit", answer: "istua", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "site", answer: "paikka", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "situation", answer: "tilanne", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "six", answer: "kuusi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "size", answer: "koko", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "ski", answer: "suksi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "skill", answer: "taito", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "skin", answer: "iho", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "sky", answer: "taivas", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "slave", answer: "orja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "sleep", answer: "nukkua", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "slice", answer: "viipale", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "slide", answer: "dia", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "slight", answer: "hienoinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "slightly", answer: "hieman", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "slip", answer: "lipsahdus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "slow", answer: "hidas", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "slowly", answer: "hitaasti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "small", answer: "pieni", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "smart", answer: "fiksu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "smell", answer: "haju", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "smile", answer: "hymy", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "smoke", answer: "savu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "smooth", answer: "sileä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "snap", answer: "napsahtaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "snow", answer: "lumi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "so", answer: "niin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "so-called", answer: "niin sanottu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "soccer", answer: "jalkapallo", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "social", answer: "sosiaalinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "society", answer: "yhteiskunta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "soft", answer: "pehmeä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "software", answer: "ohjelmisto", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "soil", answer: "maaperä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "solar", answer: "aurinko-", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "soldier", answer: "sotilas", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "solid", answer: "vankka", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "solution", answer: "ratkaisu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "solve", answer: "ratkaista", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "some", answer: "jonkin verran", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "somebody", answer: "joku", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "somehow", answer: "jollakin tavalla", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "someone", answer: "joku", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "something", answer: "jotain", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "sometimes", answer: "joskus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "somewhat", answer: "jossain määrin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "somewhere", answer: "jonnekin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "son", answer: "poika", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "song", answer: "laulu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "soon", answer: "pian", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "sophisticated", answer: "hienostunut", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "sorry", answer: "anteeksi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "sort", answer: "järjestellä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "soul", answer: "sielu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "sound", answer: "ääni", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "soup", answer: "keitto", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "source", answer: "lähde", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "south", answer: "etelä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "southern", answer: "eteläinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "soviet", answer: "neuvostoliiton", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "space", answer: "tila", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "spanish", answer: "espanja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "speak", answer: "puhua", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "speaker", answer: "kaiutin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "special", answer: "erityinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "specialist", answer: "asiantuntija", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "species", answer: "laji", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "specific", answer: "erityinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "specifically", answer: "erityisesti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "speech", answer: "puhe", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "speed", answer: "nopeus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "spend", answer: "viettää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "spending", answer: "menot", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "spin", answer: "pyöräyttää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "spirit", answer: "henki", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "spiritual", answer: "hengellinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "split", answer: "jakaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "spokesman", answer: "tiedottaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "sport", answer: "urheilu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "spot", answer: "täplä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "spread", answer: "levitä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "spring", answer: "kevät", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "square", answer: "neliö", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "squeeze", answer: "puristaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "stability", answer: "pysyvyys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "stable", answer: "vakaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "staff", answer: "henkilöstö", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "stage", answer: "vaihe", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "stair", answer: "rappu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "stake", answer: "panos", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "stand", answer: "seistä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "standard", answer: "standardi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "standing", answer: "pysyvä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "star", answer: "tähti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "stare", answer: "tuijotus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "start", answer: "alkaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "state", answer: "osavaltio", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "statement", answer: "selvitys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "station", answer: "asema", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "statistics", answer: "tilasto", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "status", answer: "tila", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "stay", answer: "pysyä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "steady", answer: "vakaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "steal", answer: "varastaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "steel", answer: "teräs", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "step", answer: "vaihe", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "stick", answer: "tikku", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "still", answer: "vielä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "stir", answer: "herättää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "stock", answer: "kalusto", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "stomach", answer: "vatsa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "stone", answer: "kivi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "stop", answer: "lopettaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "storage", answer: "varastointi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "store", answer: "myymälä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "storm", answer: "myrsky", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "story", answer: "tarina", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "straight", answer: "suoraan", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "strange", answer: "outo", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "stranger", answer: "muukalainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "strategic", answer: "strateginen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "strategy", answer: "strategia", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "stream", answer: "virta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "street", answer: "katu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "strength", answer: "vahvuus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "strengthen", answer: "vahvistaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "stress", answer: "stressi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "stretch", answer: "venyttää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "strike", answer: "lakko", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "string", answer: "jono", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "strip", answer: "kaistale", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "stroke", answer: "tahti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "strong", answer: "vahva", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "strongly", answer: "voimakkaasti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "structure", answer: "rakenne", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "struggle", answer: "kamppailu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "student", answer: "opiskelija", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "studio", answer: "studio", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "study", answer: "tutkimus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "stuff", answer: "jutut", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "stupid", answer: "tyhmä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "style", answer: "tyyli", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "subject", answer: "aihe", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "submit", answer: "lähetä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "subsequent", answer: "myöhempi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "substance", answer: "aine", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "substantial", answer: "merkittävä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "succeed", answer: "onnistua", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "success", answer: "menestys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "successful", answer: "onnistunut", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "successfully", answer: "onnistuneesti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "such", answer: "sellainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "sudden", answer: "äkillinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "suddenly", answer: "yhtäkkiä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "sue", answer: "haastaa oikeuteen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "suffer", answer: "kärsiä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "sufficient", answer: "riittävä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "sugar", answer: "sokeri", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "suggest", answer: "ehdottaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "suggestion", answer: "ehdotus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "suicide", answer: "itsemurha", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "suit", answer: "#NIMI?", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "summer", answer: "kesä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "summit", answer: "kokous", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "sun", answer: "aurinko", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "super", answer: "super", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "supply", answer: "toimittaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "support", answer: "tuki", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "supporter", answer: "tukija", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "suppose", answer: "olettaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "supposed", answer: "oletettu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "supreme", answer: "ylin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "sure", answer: "varma", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "surely", answer: "varmasti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "surface", answer: "pinta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "surgery", answer: "leikkaus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "surprise", answer: "yllätys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "surprised", answer: "yllättynyt", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "surprising", answer: "yllättävä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "surprisingly", answer: "yllättävän", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "surround", answer: "ympäröidä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "survey", answer: "tutkimus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "survival", answer: "eloonjääminen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "survive", answer: "hengissä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "survivor", answer: "selviytyjä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "suspect", answer: "epäilty", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "sustain", answer: "pitää yllä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "swear", answer: "vannoa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "sweep", answer: "lakaista", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "sweet", answer: "makea", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "swim", answer: "uida", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "swing", answer: "keinu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "switch", answer: "vaihtaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "symbol", answer: "symboli", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "symptom", answer: "oire", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "system", answer: "järjestelmä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "table", answer: "pöytä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "tablespoon", answer: "ruokalusikka", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "tactic", answer: "taktiikka", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "tail", answer: "pyrstö", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "take", answer: "ottaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "tale", answer: "tarina", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "talent", answer: "lahjakkuus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "talk", answer: "puhua", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "tall", answer: "pitkä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "tank", answer: "säiliö", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "tap", answer: "hana", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "tape", answer: "nauha", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "target", answer: "kohde", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "task", answer: "tehtävä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "taste", answer: "maku", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "tax", answer: "verottaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "taxpayer", answer: "veronmaksaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "tea", answer: "tee", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "teach", answer: "opettaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "teacher", answer: "opettaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "teaching", answer: "opetus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "team", answer: "tiimi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "tear", answer: "repiä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "teaspoon", answer: "teelusikka", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "technical", answer: "tekninen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "technique", answer: "tekniikka", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "technology", answer: "tekniikka", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "teen", answer: "teini-ikäinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "teenager", answer: "teini-ikäinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "telephone", answer: "puhelin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "telescope", answer: "teleskooppi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "television", answer: "televisio", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "tell", answer: "kertoa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "temperature", answer: "lämpötila", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "temporary", answer: "tilapäinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "ten", answer: "kymmenen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "tend", answer: "taipumus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "tendency", answer: "suuntaus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "tennis", answer: "tennis", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "tension", answer: "jännitys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "tent", answer: "teltta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "term", answer: "termi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "terms", answer: "ehdot", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "terrible", answer: "kauhea", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "territory", answer: "alue", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "terror", answer: "terrori", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "terrorism", answer: "terrorismi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "terrorist", answer: "terroristi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "test", answer: "testata", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "testify", answer: "todistaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "testimony", answer: "todistus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "testing", answer: "testaus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "text", answer: "teksti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "than", answer: "kuin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "thank", answer: "kiittää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "thanks", answer: "kiitos", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "that", answer: "että", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "the", answer: "", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "theater", answer: "teatteri", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "their", answer: "heidän", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "them", answer: "niitä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "theme", answer: "teema", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "themselves", answer: "itse", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "then", answer: "sitten", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "theory", answer: "teoria", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "therapy", answer: "terapia", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "there", answer: "siellä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "therefore", answer: "siksi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "these", answer: "nämä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "they", answer: "ne", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "thick", answer: "paksu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "thin", answer: "ohut", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "thing", answer: "asia", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "think", answer: "ajatella", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "thinking", answer: "ajattelu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "third", answer: "kolmas", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "thirty", answer: "kolmekymmentä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "this", answer: "tämä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "those", answer: "nuo", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "though", answer: "vaikka", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "thought", answer: "ajatus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "thousand", answer: "tuhat", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "threat", answer: "uhkaus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "threaten", answer: "uhata", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "three", answer: "kolme", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "throat", answer: "kurkku", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "through", answer: "kautta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "throughout", answer: "kauttaaltaan", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "throw", answer: "heittää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "thus", answer: "täten", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "ticket", answer: "lippu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "tie", answer: "solmio", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "tight", answer: "tiukka", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "time", answer: "aika", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "tiny", answer: "pikkuruinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "tip", answer: "kärki", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "tire", answer: "rengas", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "tired", answer: "väsynyt", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "tissue", answer: "kudos", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "title", answer: "otsikko", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "to", answer: "että", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "tobacco", answer: "tupakka", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "today", answer: "tänään", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "toe", answer: "varvas", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "together", answer: "yhdessä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "tomato", answer: "tomaatti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "tomorrow", answer: "huomenna", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "tone", answer: "sävy", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "tongue", answer: "kieli", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "tonight", answer: "tänä yönä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "too", answer: "liian", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "tool", answer: "työkalu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "tooth", answer: "hammas", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "top", answer: "ylin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "topic", answer: "aihe", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "toss", answer: "nakata", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "total", answer: "kaikki yhteensä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "totally", answer: "täysin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "touch", answer: "kosketus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "tough", answer: "kova", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "tour", answer: "kiertue", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "tourist", answer: "turisti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "tournament", answer: "turnaus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "toward", answer: "kohti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "towards", answer: "kohti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "tower", answer: "torni", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "town", answer: "kaupunki", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "toy", answer: "lelu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "trace", answer: "jäljittää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "track", answer: "seurata", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "trade", answer: "käydä kauppaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "tradition", answer: "perinne", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "traditional", answer: "perinteinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "traffic", answer: "liikenne", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "tragedy", answer: "tragedia", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "trail", answer: "polku", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "train", answer: "kouluttaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "training", answer: "koulutus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "transfer", answer: "siirtää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "transform", answer: "muuttaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "transformation", answer: "muutos", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "transition", answer: "siirtyminen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "translate", answer: "kääntää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "transportation", answer: "kuljetus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "travel", answer: "matkustaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "treat", answer: "kohdella", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "treatment", answer: "hoito", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "treaty", answer: "sopimus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "tree", answer: "puu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "tremendous", answer: "valtava", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "trend", answer: "trendi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "trial", answer: "oikeudenkäynti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "tribe", answer: "heimo", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "trick", answer: "temppu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "trip", answer: "matka", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "troop", answer: "joukko", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "trouble", answer: "vaivata", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "truck", answer: "kuorma-auto", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "true", answer: "totta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "truly", answer: "todella", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "trust", answer: "luottamus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "truth", answer: "totuus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "try", answer: "yrittää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "tube", answer: "putki", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "tunnel", answer: "tunneli", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "turn", answer: "vuoro", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "tv", answer: "tv", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "twelve", answer: "kaksitoista", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "twenty", answer: "kaksikymmentä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "twice", answer: "kahdesti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "twin", answer: "twin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "two", answer: "kaksi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "type", answer: "tyyppi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "typical", answer: "tyypillinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "typically", answer: "tyypillisesti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "ugly", answer: "ruma", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "ultimate", answer: "perimmäinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "ultimately", answer: "viime kädessä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "unable", answer: "kykenemätön", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "uncle", answer: "setä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "under", answer: "alla", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "undergo", answer: "läpikäydä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "understand", answer: "ymmärtää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "understanding", answer: "ymmärtäminen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "unfortunately", answer: "valitettavasti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "uniform", answer: "yhtenäinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "union", answer: "liitto", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "unique", answer: "ainutlaatuinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "unit", answer: "yksikkö", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "united", answer: "yhdistynyt", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "universal", answer: "yleismaailmallinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "universe", answer: "maailmankaikkeus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "university", answer: "yliopisto", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "unknown", answer: "tuntematon", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "unless", answer: "ellei", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "unlike", answer: "toisin kuin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "unlikely", answer: "epätodennäköistä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "until", answer: "siihen asti kun", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "unusual", answer: "epätavallinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "up", answer: "ylös", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "upon", answer: "päälle", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "upper", answer: "ylempi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "urban", answer: "kaupunki-", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "urge", answer: "halu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "us", answer: "meille", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "use", answer: "käyttää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "used", answer: "käytetyt", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "useful", answer: "hyödyllinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "user", answer: "käyttäjä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "usual", answer: "tavallinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "usually", answer: "yleensä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "utility", answer: "apuohjelma", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "vacation", answer: "loma", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "valley", answer: "laakso", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "valuable", answer: "arvokas", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "value", answer: "arvo", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "variable", answer: "muuttuja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "variation", answer: "vaihtelu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "variety", answer: "lajike", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "various", answer: "eri", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "vary", answer: "vaihdella", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "vast", answer: "valtava", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "vegetable", answer: "vihannes", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "vehicle", answer: "ajoneuvo", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "venture", answer: "hanke", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "version", answer: "versio", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "versus", answer: "vastaan", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "very", answer: "erittäin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "vessel", answer: "alus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "veteran", answer: "veteraani", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "via", answer: "kautta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "victim", answer: "uhri", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "victory", answer: "voitto", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "video", answer: "video-", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "view", answer: "näkymä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "viewer", answer: "katsoja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "village", answer: "kylä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "violate", answer: "rikkoa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "violation", answer: "rikkominen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "violence", answer: "väkivalta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "violent", answer: "väkivaltainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "virtually", answer: "käytännössä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "virtue", answer: "hyve", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "virus", answer: "virus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "visible", answer: "näkyvä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "vision", answer: "näkemys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "visit", answer: "vierailla", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "visitor", answer: "vierailija", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "visual", answer: "visuaalinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "vital", answer: "elintärkeä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "voice", answer: "ääni", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "volume", answer: "tilavuus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "volunteer", answer: "vapaaehtoinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "vote", answer: "äänestys", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "voter", answer: "äänestäjä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "vs", answer: "vs", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "vulnerable", answer: "haavoittuva", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "wage", answer: "palkka", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "wait", answer: "odota", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "wake", answer: "herätä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "walk", answer: "kävellä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "wall", answer: "seinä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "wander", answer: "vaeltaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "want", answer: "haluta", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "war", answer: "sota", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "warm", answer: "lämmetä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "warn", answer: "varoittaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "warning", answer: "varoitus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "wash", answer: "pestä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "waste", answer: "hukkaan", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "watch", answer: "katsella", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "water", answer: "vesi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "wave", answer: "aalto", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "way", answer: "tapa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "we", answer: "me", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "weak", answer: "heikko", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "wealth", answer: "rikkaus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "wealthy", answer: "varakas", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "weapon", answer: "ase", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "wear", answer: "pitää päällä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "weather", answer: "sää", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "wedding", answer: "häät", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "week", answer: "viikko", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "weekend", answer: "viikonloppu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "weekly", answer: "viikoittain", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "weigh", answer: "punnita", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "weight", answer: "paino", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "welcome", answer: "tervetuloa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "welfare", answer: "hyvinvointi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "well", answer: "hyvin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "west", answer: "länsi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "western", answer: "läntinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "wet", answer: "märkä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "what", answer: "mitä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "whatever", answer: "aivan sama", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "wheel", answer: "pyörä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "when", answer: "kun", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "whenever", answer: "milloin tahansa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "where", answer: "missä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "whereas", answer: "taas", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "whether", answer: "onko", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "which", answer: "joka", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "while", answer: "sillä aikaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "whisper", answer: "kuiskaus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "white", answer: "valkoinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "who", answer: "kuka", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "whole", answer: "koko", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "whom", answer: "ketä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "whose", answer: "jonka", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "why", answer: "miksi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "wide", answer: "leveä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "widely", answer: "laajalti", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "widespread", answer: "laajalle levinnyt", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "wife", answer: "vaimo", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "wild", answer: "villi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "will", answer: "tahtoa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "willing", answer: "halukas", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "win", answer: "voittaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "wind", answer: "tuuli", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "window", answer: "ikkuna", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "wine", answer: "viini", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "wing", answer: "siipi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "winner", answer: "voittaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "winter", answer: "talvi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "wipe", answer: "pyyhkiä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "wire", answer: "johdin", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "wisdom", answer: "viisaus", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "wise", answer: "viisas", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "wish", answer: "toive", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "with", answer: "kanssa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "withdraw", answer: "peruuttaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "within", answer: "sisällä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "without", answer: "ilman", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "witness", answer: "todistaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "woman", answer: "nainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "wonder", answer: "ihme", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "wonderful", answer: "ihana", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "wood", answer: "puu", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "wooden", answer: "puinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "word", answer: "sana", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "work", answer: "työ", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "worker", answer: "työntekijä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "working", answer: "työskentely", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "works", answer: "teokset", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "workshop", answer: "työpaja", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "world", answer: "maailman-", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "worried", answer: "huolestunut", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "worry", answer: "huoli", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "worth", answer: "arvoinen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "would", answer: "olisiko", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "wound", answer: "haava", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "wrap", answer: "kietoa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "write", answer: "kirjoittaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "writer", answer: "kirjailija", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "writing", answer: "kirjoittaminen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "wrong", answer: "väärä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "yard", answer: "piha", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "yeah", answer: "joo", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "year", answer: "vuosi", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "yell", answer: "huutaa", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "yellow", answer: "keltainen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "yes", answer: "joo", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "yesterday", answer: "eilen", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "yet", answer: "vielä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "yield", answer: "tuotto", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "you", answer: "sinä", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "young", answer: "nuori", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "your", answer: "teidän", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "yours", answer: "sinun", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "yourself", answer: "sinä itse", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "youth", answer: "nuoret", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 },
      { question: "zone", answer: "vyöhyke", countFinnish: 0 , countEnglish: 0 }
];